centercode.com 2018-10-03

# Centercode Privacy Policy | Centercode

Effective May 25th, 2018

## Introduction

The following is intended to explain how Centercode uses this website, and any information we collect, to market and sell our products, and to explain the tools, services, and technologies we leverage to do so. Above all, our goal is to always be responsible in how we collect, store, and use your information, while complying with all relevant regulations.

To simplify this for our audience, we’ve split our policy into two parts. The first section is intended to provide a walk-through of the primary ways we handle your data. These are the things that we feel are most interesting to the majority of our audience. The second section provides the comprehensive details.

Regardless, we comply with and are passionate about this entire policy, and would encourage you to take your time in reviewing it. If you have any questions, please don’t hesitate to contact us at [privacy@centercode.com](mailto:privacy@centercode.com).

### Intended Audiences

The primary audience of this website is businesses interested in learning more about Centercode and its offerings. The secondary audiences are individuals seeking employment at Centercode, vendors, and others seeking to have a business relationship with us.

If you’re not with a business, or looking for a job, but rather are an individual interested in testing new products, you should instead visit our [Betabound](https://betabound.com/) portal (which has its own [Privacy Policy](https://betabound.com/privacy)). Betabound is always looking for enthusiastic testers.

Alternatively, if you’re a company actively using the Centercode Platform or our services, or are a user of such a company, please see our Customer Data Handling Policies.

## Data Handling Overview

The following explains how your data is handled as you navigate and interact with Centercode and our website.

### Visitor Tracking

When you visit our website, your activity as you navigate is tracked by [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/analytics/web/) and [Marketo](https://www.marketo.com/) via cookies. Google Analytics lets us study aggregated (or de-identified) data about our traffic patterns in order to improve our site design and the information we offer. Marketo tracks your ongoing activity on our site. If at some point you choose to provide information to us that reveals your identity, then your prior activity will be matched to your new record in Marketo. This is intended to help us to prioritize our efforts by focusing on our most engaged visitors.

### Gated Content

We offer significant industry and educational resources on our site. These include things like white papers, ebooks, and recorded webinars, and are typically “gated”, meaning we require information from you in order to download them. Our goal in investing significant resources in developing these valuable materials is to create an opportunity to learn about you and begin building a relationship. To achieve this goal, we use Marketo to collect your full name and job title, email address, phone number, company name and size, and the intent of your download (e.g. researching vs. interested in purchasing).

We use this information to determine your likely interest in our offerings. If we feel we’re a fit, the information we collected is sent to our CRM System ([Insightly](https://insightly.com/)). We use [Zapier](https://zapier.com/) to make this transfer, and leverage a platform known as [Clearbit](https://clearbit.com/) to enrich this data, reducing what we need to ask of you directly.

If we feel you’re an ideal prospect, a member of our internal account team will study your company and reach out to attempt to continue to build a relationship with you, in the hope that there will be an opportunity to work together. Our team is not pushy, and are trained to be as consultative as possible. If you ask that they stop contacting you, they’ll politely and immediately respect your wishes, and follow an internal process to remove your data.

By downloading our gated content, you’ll likely receive marketing email from us, such as future content and webinar announcements. We consider your attention limited and time valuable, and therefore deliberately limit our outreach. In addition, every email will include a very simple opt-out mechanism, which will remove you from future outreach.

### Other Web Site Activities

Beyond downloading content, there are a few other ways to engage with us that do collect personal or use information.

  * **In-Site Chat** – You’ll notice a small circle in the bottom right of our site. This allows you to communicate with us in real-time via [Intercom](https://intercom.com/). While you don’t need to provide any personal information to use our real-time chat (and we don’t send information to it), your email will be requested if we’re not actively available, so that we can get back to you. 
  * **Webinar Registration** – If you happen to participate in any of our webinars, the [Zoom](https://zoom.us/) platform will collect basic contact information in order to access our live webinar event. Recorded webinars do not require interacting with Zoom. 
  * **Event Registration** – If you register to attend one of our live events (e.g. Conference, Roadshows), your contact information will be collected and stored on the [Bizzabo](https://bizzabo.com/) events management platform. 
  * **Meeting Scheduling** – If you schedule a meeting with our team, we’ll collect basic contact information and schedule preferences via the [YouCanBookMe](https://youcanbook.me/) platform. Alternatively, our sales team uses [Calendly](https://calendly.com/) for individual meeting scheduling. 
  * **Email, Calendar, and Drive** – Our back-office productivity platform is the business version of [G Suite](https://gsuite.google.com/) , including Gmail, Google Calendar, and Google Drive. If we interact with you directly, these email and calendar details will be stored by Google. 
  * **Job Applications** – If you apply for a job on our site, you’ll be asked to provide information relevant to the position via to the [JazzHR](https://jazzhr.com/) Applicant Tracking system. We use this platform for all applicant communication and scheduling. 

Where relevant, these systems typically feed information to or from Marketo (for marketing automation) and Insightly (for CRM), which are our primary marketing and sales platforms. Our goal is to always centralize information as much as possible, but in every case, **we manage your data, know where it is, and how to delete it.**

Finally, it’s important to understand that we only use your information for our own purposes. **We never sell your information, and none of the systems or partners that we leverage have that right.**

## Detailed Policy

This policy describes how Centercode collects, uses, and discloses information, and the choices you have about the information we collect. When we refer to **Centercode** , we mean **Centercode, Inc.** , a California corporation.

Centercode owns and operates the Centercode.com website and runs its business of providing Customer Validation services to businesses developing products based on its cloud-based software platform known as the Centercode Platform.

Centercode also owns and operates [Betabound](https://betabound.com/), the web-based test participation portal known as Betabound, which we use to announce a wide variety of third-party Customer Validation opportunities, and to register and collect information about individuals interested in participating in Customer Validation tests. Our Betabound offerings are outside of the scope of this Centercode Privacy Policy (see Scope).

You should read this entire privacy policy. If you do not agree to its terms, you should not use our sites or services or submit personal information or other content to us. By using our sites or services and/or providing data to us you are accepting and agreeing to the practices outlined in this privacy policy.

* * *

## Table of Contents

  * Scope
  * The Data We Collect and Receive
    * Centercode Business Visitor and Contact Information
    * Centercode Customer Contact and Billing Information
    * Centercode Job Applicant Information
    * Other Information
  * How We Use and Share Personal Data
    * Centercode Visitor, Business, and Other Contact Information
    * Job Applicants
    * Aggregated or De-Identified Information
    * Other Use and Sharing
    * How We Share Data with Our Third-Party Service Providers and Partners
  * Cookies, IP Addresses, and Other Passive Information Collected
    * Third-Party Cookies and Opting Out
    * Do Not Track
  * Security
  * Updating Email Preferences
  * Data Retention
  * Data Modification, Deletion, and Other Rights
  * Links to Third-Party Sites
  * Data of Children
  * International Transfer of Data
  * Changes to Our Privacy Policy
  * Questions or Concerns

* * *

## Scope

This privacy policy describes our privacy practices related to information that we collect through or related to Centercode.com, and our Centercode social media pages (collectively, the **Centercode Sites** ), and information that we collect related to Centercode employment, vendor relationships, and business services.

This policy does not describe our practices for the information that we collect through or related to the Betabound web-based test participation portal, Betabound social media pages, emails, and other communications related to Betabound (collectively, the **Betabound Sites** ). If you’re a visitor to the Betabound Sites, an account holder on the Betabound portal, or otherwise encounter our platform inside of Betabound, please visit the [Betabound Privacy Policy](https://betabound.com/privacy/) to learn about our privacy practices that apply to you.

Finally, some of the information we collect or process is collected by or on behalf of our customers in connection with the services we offer to our customers. This information and the use of the Centercode Platform is beyond the scope of this policy. For more information about data that we hold and process for our customers, please read about our Customer Data Handling Practices.

## The Data We Collect and Receive

In order to operate and enable your use of the Centercode Sites, operate our business and services, and for other legitimate business interests described in this policy, we receive and collect certain information from you and about you, which includes **Personal Data**.

When we use the term **Personal Data** , we mean information that identifies an individual or that relates to an identified or identifiable individual (e.g. name, email address, phone number, location data, mailing address).

**By submitting or providing Personal Data or other information to us, you are representing that you have authority to do so and that we have full authorization to use this information in accordance with this privacy policy, even if the information relates to other individuals or entities.**

### Centercode Business Visitor and Contact Information

When you request more information or otherwise contact us through the Centercode Sites or otherwise (e.g. when you request a free trial or demo, register for a webinar, download content, complete a contact form, attend one of our events, interact through our social media pages, email, or call us), we may collect Personal Data such as your name, title, company name, job function, address, telephone number, email address, and other Personal Data and information that you voluntarily provide to us. If this occurs online, we may also collect the time, date, and location of the form you submitted.

### Centercode Customer Contact and Billing Information

When customers establish services, we may collect, process, and use Personal Data such as name and address, company name and details, work contact information, financial, payment, and billing information, and other Personal Data and information that the customer voluntarily provides to us, such as when a customer contact completes a form or calls or submits an email to our sales, customer support, or services teams. We process this data through our trusted third-party service providers, including billing and credit card processing providers.

### Centercode Job Applicant Information

When you inquire about employment with Centercode, we collect Personal Data such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, a resume, a cover letter, your profile information, a statement of interest regarding your desired position, and similar Personal Data. We also collect the time, date, and location of the information you submitted.

When you apply for a job on our site, the information you provide goes to the JazzHR Applicant Tracking system. We use this platform for all applicant communication and scheduling. As with the other third-party services we use, JazzHR holds your data on our behalf in order to provide services to us.

### Other Information

We may collect information from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, social media platforms, and from other third parties (such as Clearbit) in order to enhance our ability to provide relevant marketing, offers, and content to you. The information we collect this way is from publicly accessible sources, such as business details and business contact information (e.g. your name, business email, address, and phone number, and job title), and social media handles. We may also collect, track, and analyze non-identifying statistical, anonymous, or aggregated information from visitors and users of the Centercode Sites. Also, we passively collect data, as disclosed below in our policy regarding Cookies, IP Addresses, and Other Passive Information Collection.

## How We Use and Share Personal Data

This section describes how we use and share (or disclose) information within the scope of this policy.

### Centercode Visitor, Business, and Other Contact Information

We use contact information that you have provided as a visitor to the Centercode Sites or through your business or other contacts in order to contact you to discuss your interest in the services we offer, and to send you information such as announcements of business-related opportunities and events. Where you provide us with your contact information, we may also send you community newsletters and updates. If at any time you no longer wish to receive these communications, you can follow the instructions under Updating Email Preferences

We also use customer contact information to initiate services with our customers, including providing the customer’s appointed representatives with access to the customer’s account on the Centercode Platform.

The use of and information collected by the Centercode Platform is outside the scope of this privacy policy. For more information about data that we hold and process for our customers, please review our Customer Data Handling Practices.

### Job Applicants

We use information that you submit in connection with your interest in employment to review your job application, notify you about future hiring events and job openings, and communicate with you through the hiring process.

### Aggregated or De-Identified Information

Where data is aggregated or de-identified so that it is no longer reasonably associated with an identified or identifiable natural person, we may use and disclose it for any business purpose, except as otherwise prohibited under applicable law. Typically this would be used for research purposes, or to promote our services, but we may have other business uses.

### Other Use and Sharing

We may also use and share the information you provide to us for other legitimate interests, including

  * to create an account you have requested or your employer has requested; 
  * to send administrative information to you, such as changes to our terms, conditions, and policies; 
  * to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as to send you requested materials and newsletters, as well as information about our services and businesses; 
  * to service your account or the account of your company, including maintaining records of any agreements you or your company enters into; 
  * to personalize your experience on the Centercode Sites, such as by presenting content tailored to you or your company; 
  * for our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, network and information security, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our sites and services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, and operating or expanding our business activities; 
  * in connection with company transactions such as asset sales, reorganizations, mergers, joint ventures, assignments, financings, dispositions of stock, and other changes of control, where Personal Data and other information is transferred to third parties for legitimate purposes in connection with the transactions; 
  * as we believe to be necessary or appropriate under applicable law, including laws outside of your country of residence, to comply with legal process, to respond to the requests of courts or governmental authorities, to enforce our terms and conditions, to protect our operations, rights, privacy, safety, customers, or property (or that of others), and to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit damages we may sustain; and 
  * for other purposes you have specifically agreed to. 

### How We Share Data with Our Third-Party Service Providers and Partners

We contract with third-party service providers and partners who provide services to us in accordance with our instructions, such as those that we have identified in this policy. In addition, we use cloud hosting providers (such as Amazon Web Services and Rackspace), shipping providers (e.g. UPS, FedEx, USPS), and general office services such as email and file storage (e.g. Google). These third parties may have access to your data (including Personal Data) for the purpose of providing services to us and in compliance with our documented instructions. We diligently choose these third-party service providers, evaluate their privacy, security, and confidentiality practices, and enter into agreements with them specifying their obligations.

## Cookies, IP Addresses, and Other Passive Information Collected

Like many companies, we use cookies (small data files stored on your computer), logging, and similar tools to collect and analyze information about our visitors and site usage. This information is used to operate the Centercode Sites, to prevent fraud and misuse of our services, to measure how people use the Centercode Sites, to analyze how people respond to our emails and other communications, to analyze trends, to improve our services, and to improve your overall experience.

### Third-Party Cookies and Opting Out

**Google Analytics Cookies** : We use Google Analytics cookies, which allow us to analyze how our visitors and users interact with the Centercode Sites. The information generated about your usage is transmitted to Google and is used to compile statistical reports on activity on the Centercode Sites to help us improve these sites and your experience. The information we receive from Google Analytics is aggregated data and we cannot use it to individually identify any particular visitor or user. We encourage you to read the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

If you don’t want data collected by Google Analytics, you can use a [browser plugin by Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to opt-out.

**Marketo Cookies** : These Marketo-placed cookies help us to understand your interactions with the emails and other communications we send you, track your visits to the Centercode Sites (including the dates and times of your visits), and provide you with information that may be of interest to you about our services and business. For example, Marketo cookies let us know whether our emails have been opened, which links are clicked, and how many unique visitors we have.

This information generated about your usage is transmitted to Marketo in the United States. The information we receive from Marketo cookies and tracking technologies does not, standing alone, personally identify you. However, if you have chosen to identify yourself to us, such as by providing personal information when responding to a promotional offer, filling out a web form, or downloading content, we may re-associate this information with the personal information you have provided to us. We encourage you to read the [Marketo Privacy Policy](http://legal.marketo.com/privacy/). To learn generally how to opt out of cookies using your browser settings and other tracking technologies, you may wish to visit the [FTC’s Online Tracking informational page](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0042-online-tracking).

These services may work by use of other standard technologies, such as web beacons, clear gifs, and similar tracking technologies.

### Do Not Track

We do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” browser signals.

## Security

We take the security of the Personal Data that we hold very seriously. We maintain a written security policy for the security, integrity, and protection of the Personal Data we hold against unauthorized disclosure or loss. We have put in place physical, technical, and organizational processes and measures designed to safeguard all Personal Data.

These safeguards help prevent accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorised disclosure of, or access to, the Personal Data that we hold. However, you should be aware that no security procedures or protocols are guaranteed to be 100% secure, and there is always some risk assumed when you share information.

If you have reason to believe that your Personal Data with us is no longer secure or you would like more information about our security practices, please contact us at [privacy@centercode.com](mailto:privacy@centercode.com). In the event that any Personal Data under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will investigate the situation and, where appropriate or required by law, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

## Updating Email Preferences

To opt out of receiving emails or communications from us, please contact us at [optout@centercode.com](mailto:optout@centercode.com). We will respond promptly.

## Data Retention

We will retain your Personal Data for a period of time consistent with the original purpose of collection, including to pursue our legitimate business interests, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements.

## Data Modification, Deletion, and Other Rights

Individuals located in certain countries, including those residing in the European Union, the European Economic Area, and Switzerland (“ **European Residents** ”), have certain statutory rights regarding their Personal Data. For European Residents, reference to “Personal Data” in this privacy policy is equivalent to “Personal Data” as defined in the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Subject to any exemptions provided by law, these individuals may have the right to request access to their Personal Data, or seek to update, delete, or correct Personal Data. If your request relates to Personal Data within the scope of the GDPR, your rights may be exercised by contacting [privacy@centercode.com](mailto:privacy@centercode.com). Any European Resident who is dissatisfied with our handling of a request regarding Personal Data within the scope of the GDPR, has a right to lodge a complaint with his or her local data protection authority responsible for monitoring the application of the GDPR.

If your request relates to information that we hold and process for our customer, please contact our customer, or for more information, read Customer Data Handling Practices.

For your protection, we may need to verify your identity before implementing any request relating to your Personal Data. We will respond to your request promptly, and in no more than 30 days from your request, subject to applicable law. Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes, such as retaining copies of agreements you have entered into with us and/or for audit and investigation purposes, or in the event of a court order or requirement of law.

Deleted or updated Personal Data stored in our backup systems will be automatically deleted or updated within a reasonable period of time during our backup procedures, except as otherwise required by applicable law.

## Links to Third-Party Sites

The Centercode Sites and emails that come from us may contain links to other websites on the Internet. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of all such third parties. **Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy policies and collection, use, and disclosure practices (including the data security practices) of these third parties, including those that are our customers.**

## Data of Children

The Centercode Sites are not intended for use by minors under the age of 16. We do not knowingly or specifically collect information from these minors through the Centercode Sites or otherwise. If you believe that we have mistakenly or unintentionally collected information from minors or have any questions or concerns regarding the use of our services to collect information from minors, please contact us at [privacy@centercode.com](mailto:privacy@centercode.com) so that we may investigate and delete the information from our servers as necessary.

## International Transfer of Data

The Personal Data and other information we collect from you is used, stored, and/or processed by us in the United States, where we are located. In addition, in the circumstances described in this privacy policy where your Personal Data and other information is transferred to a third party (such as our service provider), this data may also be used, stored, and/or processed outside of the United States in any country in which the third party has facilities or engages service providers. These countries may not offer the same legal protections offered in your country and may be considered by your country to offer insufficient legal protections.

European Residents have a right to withdraw their consent to cross-border transfers of their data, and if you wish to do so with respect to your Personal Data that we control, you may contact us at [privacy@centercode.com](mailto:privacy@centercode.com). The withdrawal of consent will not affect the lawfulness of actions based on your consent prior to your withdrawal. If your request relates to information that is Centercode Customer Data, you will find more information in our Customer Data Handling Practices.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy. If we make changes to this policy, you will find the revised privacy policy posted on the Centercode Sites, along with the effective date of the revised privacy policy. Your use of and access to the Centercode Sites after any changes become effective will be considered your acceptance of those changes and will constitute your agreement to be bound by the new or modified privacy policy.

## Questions or Concerns

Questions about this Privacy Policy or our information practices should be directed to Centercode by emailing [privacy@centercode.com](mailto:privacy@centercode.com) or by mailing us at **23332 Mill Creek Drive, Suite 260, Laguna Hills, CA 92653 ATTN: Privacy Policy**.

Alternatively, to communicate with our Data Protection Officer, please email [dpo@centercode.com](mailto:dpo@centercode.com), or by mail at **23332 Mill Creek Drive, Suite 260, Laguna Hills, CA 92653 ATTN: DPO** , or by phone at **(800) 705-6540**.
